ICICI Lombard presented better results than expected
and especially when the
insurance company does
not expect good results, then ICICI
gave us some relief. I think there will be an upside of around 2 to 3%
and the
stock should increase by that much, it can also increase more
because the stock did
not move much and people have
made a lot of bullish positions in the insurance company,
so it can give a little surprise. The numbers are
good, there is no doubt in this, so far
if you look at the insurance company from today, it
presented good numbers and the
stock should increase a little from here and anyway the
stock has not closed much higher before the fall,
so there is scope, according to
me, there is room for 2 to 3%.
ICICI Lombard has given very good results,
like this the potential is a little
weak, but here the net premium end has
increased by 18% this time and the profit is
also above 32%. Hanuman, which was seen giving very
good results, the claim ratio has been
sustained this time and remains around 73%.
Rakha Laxmi Bada is increased from 1470 to
1550, the closing is around 1150
brother, if you see, JP Morgan has
maintained the neutral rating and
they have reduced the target from 1300 to 1200,
credit cheese has
kept outperform creation, the
target is 1430 and I have barred acquired underperform
greeting for ₹995, if you
look at the dating, no one has made any changes
but everyone is saying that if you see the results, they are saying that they are
quite
good from the profitability point of view, due to which if you look
at the estimates of the apps, they have increased it not much, but by about 1 to
3% and going forward, the
growth horizon is also very good expected,
ICICI Lombard Kunal
ji, please take a look at its chart as well, the
result is good here too sir,
look, after a long time some positive
development is visible on the chart here,
Deepanshu, we have taken a look at the lower levels  We have
seen a base forming and if you look at yesterday's trade as
well, there is a spectacular recovery from the lower levels,
so I think there will be an upside
here today as well. It remains to be seen
how big a rally this episode will translate into.
I think there is
multiple resistance in the stock. The first
star which is the critical resistance is
1200 and after that there are levels of 1240,
so the target of 1240 should be dreamed of. Those who
have a long position should stay put for now.
Okay, so if you have a long position then stay put.
This is
such a Lombard for you. Let's see how
it will perform. After the straight opening today,
you have seen good numbers coming in.